http://www.coorstek.com/english/legal-conditions-privacy-policy/

Semiconductor Wafers
Semiconductor Fabrication (front end)
Semiconductor Fabrication (front end)
Diffusion & LPCVD Processing
Wafer Planarization (CMP)
Material Comparison Tool
Why Ceramics?
Why Ceramics?
CoorsTek Terms & Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy
YOUR USE OF THIS SITE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO BE BOUND BY AND COMPLY WITH THE CONDITIONS OF WEBSITE AND YOUR CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE AND CONSENT, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO VISIT OR USE OUR WEBSITE.
If you have questions and/or comments regarding our Website, you may contact us as provided in the Contact Us section of our Privacy Policy.
PLEASE READ THESE DOCUMENTS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITE
Conditions of Website
Ownership and Use of Materials on this Site(s)
Submissions
Monitoring
Links to Other Sites
Trademarks
Export Control
Disclaimer
Legal Documents
Limitation of Liabilities
Indemnification
Changes to this Site(s)
Termination
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
International Users and Applicable Laws
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Conditions of WebsiteLast Updated July 12, 2016
These Conditions of Website are entered into by and between You and CoorsTek, Inc. The following terms and conditions govern your access to this this website and other CoorsTek related websites referenced herein. Please read these Conditions of Website carefully before you start to use the Website. By using the Website you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Conditions of Website and other policies referenced herein. If you do not want to agree to these Conditions of Website, you must not access or use the Website.
This Site is owned and operated by CoorsTek, Inc. (referred to as "CoorsTek," "we," "us," or "our" herein). Subject to the terms and conditions set forth herein, information (“Materials”) from coorstek.com or any website owned, operated, licensed or controlled by CoorsTek ("Sites") may not be copied, reproduced, republished, modified, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, except as set forth below. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of this site in any way.
OwnershipCoorsTek authorizes you to view and download the Materials at its Site(s) only for your personal, non-commercial use. This authorization is not a transfer of title in the Materials and copies of the Materials are subject to the following restrictions: 1) you must retain, on all copies of the Materials downloaded, all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Materials; 2) you may not modify the Materials in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose; and 3) you must not transfer the Materials to any other person unless you give them notice of, and they agree to accept, the obligations arising under these terms and conditions of use. You agree to abide by all additional restrictions displayed on the Site(s) as it may be updated from time to time without notice. This Site(s), including all Materials, is copyrighted and protected by worldwide copyright laws and treaty provisions. You agree to comply with all copyright laws worldwide in your use of this Site(s) and to prevent any unauthorized copying of the Materials. Except as expressly provided herein, CoorsTek does not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, trademarks, copyrights or trade secret information. If you breach any of these Terms and Conditions of Use, your authorization to use this Site(s) will automatically terminate and you must immediately destroy or delete any downloaded or printed material. CoorsTek reserves its right to alter, change or amend its authorization for your use of the Materials at this site.
SubmissionsCoorsTek company policy does not allow it to accept or consider confidential creative ideas, suggestions, inventions or materials other than those it has specifically requested in writing. If, despite our request that you not send us any creative materials, you send us creative suggestions, ideas, notes, drawings, concepts, inventions or other information (collectively, the "Information"), the Information shall be deemed, and shall remain the property of CoorsTek. None of the Information shall be subject to any obligation of confidentiality on the part of CoorsTek and CoorsTek shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of any Information. You hereby warrant that all Information provided by you does not infringe upon any third party rights.
MonitoringCoorsTek will have the right, but not the obligation, to review communications with the Site(s) to determine that they comply with this Agreement and applicable laws or regulations. CoorsTek shall have no responsibility or liability for the content of any information posted to the Site(s), nor for any errors or violations of any laws. CoorsTek will comply with court orders in any jurisdiction directing CoorsTek to disclose the identity of anyone posting communications to the Site(s).
Links to Third-Party WebsitesCoorsTek is not responsible for the content of any other site linked to or from this Site(s). If you link to another site, you leave this Site(s). If you decide to link to another site, you do so entirely at your own risk. CoorsTek may provide links from this Site(s) to other sites, but this is done solely as a convenience to you and in no way should be interpreted as an endorsement of any content, sponsor or owner of any other site. ALL WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS OR OTHER TERMS EXPRESS OR IMPLIED AS TO ANY SUCH LINKED SITE INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY TERMS AS TO ACCURACY, OWNERSHIP, VALIDITY OR LEGALITY OF ANY CONTENT OF A LINKED SITE ARE HEREBY EXCLUDED.
TrademarksCoorsTek owns all rights to use of the trademarks and service marks ("Trademarks") which appear on this Site(s), unless otherwise noted. Nothing in this Site(s) should be construed as granting – by implication, estoppel, or otherwise – any license or right to use any trademarks displayed on the Site(s) without the express written permission of CoorsTek or the trademark owner, the name "CoorsTek" or the CoorsTek logos may not be used in any way without CoorsTek’s prior written consent.
You may not use the CoorsTek logos as a "hot" link to any other site unless the establishment of such a link is approved by CoorsTek in advance and in writing.
A partial list of the CoorsTek U.S. Trademarks follows. Any questions regarding the use of these Trademarks or potentially related marks should be referred to CoorsTek at (303) 277-4650. The Trademarks below followed by a registered trademark symbol(®) are registered trademarks.
Aggressor™
Amazing Solutions®
Aristorum®
CePure™
CeraCheck®
CeraFan®
CeraHive™
CeraLase™
Wilbanks®
Export ControlYou acknowledge that U.S. export control laws and regulations apply to this Site(s), including the Export Administration Regulations of the U.S. Department of Commerce and the International Traffic in Arms Regulations of the U.S. Department of State, which prohibit the export or re-export of articles, services, software, technology and information (herein referred to as “Controlled Items”) to certain countries and persons. You agree to comply strictly with all U.S. export laws and regulations and assume sole responsibility for obtaining any required licenses to export or re-export Controlled Items. You shall not export or re-export Controlled Items into (or to a national of) any country to which the United States embargoes or sanctions the Controlled Items or to any proscribed person, group or entity. In addition, you are responsible for complying with any local laws in your country which may impact your right to import, export or use the Controlled Items accessed or described on the Site(s).
This Site(s) and the information or materials contained in or described on the Site(s) shall not be accessed or used by any national of proscribed countries or groups against which the United States has instituted sanctions, Specially Designated Nationals, and other proscribed persons or entities. YOUR ACCESS OF THE SITE CONSTITUTES YOUR EXPRESS REPRESENTATION THAT THE PERSON OR ENTITY ATTEMPTING ACCESS:
(1) Is NOT a national of any such sanctioned country or group; and, (2) Is NOT a Specially Designated National; and, (3) Is NOT included on the Denied Parties List, Entity List or the Table of Denial Orders
DisclaimerTHE MATERIALS MAY CONTAIN INACCURACIES AND TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT ALLOWED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE MATERIALS PROVIDED AT THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND ANY WARRANTY, CONDITION OR OTHER TERM OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY IS HEREBY EXCLUDED. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. CoorsTek does not warrant the accuracy and completeness of the Materials on this Site(s). CoorsTek takes no responsibility for viruses or other destructive or intrusive computer programs that may damage your computer system or data resulting from your access to or use of this Site(s). CoorsTek may make changes to the Materials at this Site(s), or to the products and prices described therein, at any time and without notice. The Materials at this Site(s) may be out of date, and CoorsTek makes no commitment to update the Materials at this Site(s). Information published at this Site(s) may refer to products, programs or services that are not available in your geographic location.
Limitation of LiabilitiesIN NO EVENT WILL COORSTEK OR ITS SUPPLIERS, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SITE, ANY WEB SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE, OR THE MATERIALS OR INFORMATION CONTAINED AT ANY OR ALL SUCH SITES, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND WHETHER OR NOT COORSTEK IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IF YOUR USE OF THE MATERIALS OR COMMUNICATIONS FROM THIS SITE RESULTS IN THE NEED FOR SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION OF EQUIPMENT OR DATA, YOU ASSUME ALL COSTS THEREOF. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
IndemnificationUpon CoorsTek’s request, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless CoorsTek and its affiliates, representatives, officers, directors and employees from all liabilities, claims, costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees and costs, that arise out of or in connection with your accessing or use of the Site(s) or your uploading, downloading or transmission of all communications or material on the Site(s).
Changes to This Site(s)Please note that this Site(s) and these Terms and Conditions of Use may be revised at any time and without notice. By entering this website, you acknowledge and agree that you shall be bound by any such revisions. Accordingly, you should periodically visit this page to review these terms and conditions.
TerminationThese Terms and Conditions of Use are effective until terminated by either party. You may terminate these Terms and Conditions of Use at any time by destroying all materials obtained from any and all CoorsTek’s Site(s) and all related documentation and all copies and installations thereof, whether made under the terms of this these Terms and Conditions of Use or otherwise. These Terms and Conditions of Use will terminate immediately without notice from CoorsTek if in CoorsTek’s sole discretion and judgment you fail to comply with any term or provision stated herein. Upon termination, you shall destroy any Materials obtained from this Site(s) and any and all other CoorsTek Site(s) and all copies thereof, whether made under the terms of these Terms and Conditions of Use or otherwise.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction  All matters relating to the Conditions of Website and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims), shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Colorado without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule (whether of the State of Colorado or any other jurisdiction).
Any legal suit, action or proceeding arising out of, or related to, these Conditions of Website shall be instituted exclusively in the federal courts of the United States or the courts of the State of Colorado in each case located in the City of Denver and County of Denver although we retain the right to bring any suit, action or proceeding against you for breach of these Conditions of Website in your country of residence or any other relevant country. You waive any and all objections to the exercise of jurisdiction over you by such courts and to venue in such courts.
International Users and Applicable LawsThis Site(s) is operated, controlled and administered from CoorsTek’s offices in Colorado, United States of America. It can be accessed from any of the 50 states in the United States and from other countries of the world. By accessing this Site(s) you agree that the laws of Colorado (without regard to its conflicts of law provisions) will apply to all matters arising out of or in connection with the Site(s) and your connection to and use of the Site(s). Both parties submit to exclusive jurisdiction in Colorado and further agree that any cause of action arising out of or in connection with this Agreement shall be brought only in the federal or state courts in Jefferson County, Colorado. You further agree that any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of the Site(s) must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises.
CoorsTek makes no representation or warranty that any communications or materials on the Site(s) are lawful in other jurisdictions or available for use in all jurisdictions, and accessing them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You agree that if you access our Site(s) from another jurisdiction that you are responsible for compliance with local laws. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions of Use is held to be invalid or unenforceable, that provision will be deemed to be restated to reflect as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties in accordance with applicable law, and the remainder of the Terms and Conditions of Use will remain in full force and effect.
Privacy PolicyEffective Date: May 1, 2018
CoorsTek group companies (collectively, "CoorsTek", "we", "us", or "our") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information.
Personal information, sometimes also referred to as personal data or personally identifiable information, means any information that identifies you, either alone or in combination with other information available to us.
This privacy policy describes how CoorsTek processes your personal information when you use our website, purchase products or services from us, sign up for a newsletter, or contact us for information.
Download the full CoorsTek Privacy Policy
Contact UsYou may contact us for any reason by email or traditional mail at the following addresses, provided, however, if you wish to provide us with formal notice under our Terms and Conditions of Use or our Privacy Policy, you must provide your notice in writing, and mail it to the address set forth below:
By mail:Attention: LegalCoorsTek, Inc.14143 Denver West Pkwy.Golden, CO 80401  USA
By email:CoorsTek Legal Department
legal documents & Disclosures
Conflict Minerals Statement (1.5 MB, .xlsx file download)
Paris Public Annual Report (Paris, ON, Canada)
Paris Table A.3 Toxic Change Summary (Paris, ON, Canada)
Paris, Ontario Public Plan Posting, Toxic Reduction Plan
California Transparency in Supply Chains Act, Supplier Disclosure Statement
(toll free in North America)
Please fill out the below form to continue with the download
